This beach is killer.
The Sand is a horror, science fiction, comedy film directed by Isaac Gabaeff.
After an all-night graduation beach party, a group of hung-over students wakes up
under the blazing sun to find their numbers somewhat depleted.
An enormous alien creature has burrowed down deep and anyone foolish enough to make contact
with the sand finds themselves at the mercy of a sea of flesh-eating tentacles.
Will they ever be able to escape its carnivorous clutches?
Kaylee, played by Brooke Butler.
Gilbert, played by Cleo Berry.
Ronnie, played by Cynthia Murell.
Jonah, played by Dean Geyer.
Chanda, played by Meagan Holder.
Mitch, played by Mitchel Musso.
Sand Castle is a 2017 American war drama film directed by
Fernando Coimbra and written by Chris Roessner.
The film stars Nicholas Hoult, Logan Marshall-Green, Henry Cavill, Glen
Powell, Tommy Flanagan, Beau Knapp, and Neil Brown Jr.
The film centers on Matt Ocre, a young soldier in the United States Army,
who is tasked with restoring water to a village in Iraq.
It is inspired by Roessner's experience as a soldier in the Iraq War.
It was released on April 21, 2017, on Netflix.
The film explores themes of beach, sand, alien, stranded, eaten alive.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.